mobilecityonline.com 2002-12-11

# Mobile City online store.

**Terms and Conditions of MOBILECITYONLINE.COM use:**  
   
---  
   The use of this site is governed by the terms and conditions set forth below. Please read all of these terms and conditions carefully as the use of this site and ordering of products through this site indicate your acceptance of all of these terms. If you do not agree with these terms please discontinue your use of our site. MOBILECITYONLINE.COM reserves the right to modify, alter, or update all or any part of these site terms at any time. Please review these terms prior to each use of this site to verify that conditions and terms have not changed since your last visit to our site.   
   
   Please note that MOBILECITYONLINE.COM does link to other websites. Please be aware that our privacy policy is our own and does not apply to these linked sites. We strongly encourage you to read the terms and conditions posted on websites that you visit, as well as the policies of the vendors from whom you may choose to purchase products through this site.   
   
   MOBILECITYONLINE.COM offers you products and services in a secure manner. In order to provide you with the full benefits of our site, we require certain personal information. We collect e-mail addresses, names, address, etc on an opt-in basis.   
   
   We track use on our site by logging Internet protocol (IP) addresses and browser types, but we do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information. We also use these IP addresses for administration of the site.   
   
   You can browse our site without entering any personal information and, therefore, remain anonymous during your visit to MOBILECITYONLINE.COM   
   
   While many sections of this site may be browsed through without any personal information, access to some products and services requires registration in order to complete any transactions you want to make. We do use "cookies" to let us know that you are a returning customer or that you found us through a particular site or advertisement. Using cookies, we can provide customized content that will be interesting and useful, as well as make navigation of our site easier for the user. Our site also uses cookies to keep track of items located in your shopping cart. If you are uncomfortable with cookie technology you may change the preferences on your browser accordingly.   
   
   When you buy a product, you are asked to provide us with contact information that may include: name, address, employer info. (if any), a shipping address (must be same as credit card billing address), social security number, date of birth, credit card number, credit card expiration date, or a photo identification number (such as your driver license number). We use this information to process and fulfill your order and to protect you from false purchases made in your name.   
   
   In all instances in which you provide your personal information to us it is in a manner that is direct and clearly identifiable. Information that is collected in the process of taking and fulfilling an order is used solely for that purpose. In order to fulfill your order, we may give only that information that is necessary to fulfill the order to a third party so they may use it for activation or fulfillment purposes. MOBILECITYONLINE.COM is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We do not sell your personal information to anyone, at any time, for any purpose. We will not sell, share, or rent this information in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.   
   
   Your contact and shipping information is given only to the service provider, the manufacturer making the product you purchased, and the delivery service. Your personal credit information is forwarded only to a third-party credit card approval service to verify your credit history and to your wireless service provider to authorize credit according to their terms. All information is SSL encrypted, the industry? standard security measure, before it is sent over the Internet.   
   
   MOBILECITYONLINE.COM employs powerful 128-bit encryption technology and Secure Socket Layers (SSL) in all areas where personal information is required. For your protection. This is your assurance that our site is authentic and that we are employing SSL security. You can check this security protection setting within your browser. To view our Thawte certificate, click on the image of the closed lock or the solid key at the bottom of your browser. Our site security information will appear. Your account information and order history are kept safely behind our firewall on separate servers so you need not worry about this information being intercepted. All transaction information is processed under encrypted channels, although you always have the option to choose unencrypted processing. To be sure you have the most protection available, be sure to download the latest version of your browser. In addition, access to your personal information is restricted within our company to provide additional security. If you have any concerns about the security of our site please send an email to [INFO@MOBILECITYONLINE.COM](mailto:INFO@MOBILECITYONLINE.COM)   
   
   MOBILECITYONLINE.COM uses your information to follow-up on your order and to send you updated information on our company, new products, services, and promotions. Your service provider and manufacturer may also send you similar information. You may opt-out of receiving such information from MOBILECITYONLINE.COM by contacting our customer service department via e-mail [INFO@MOBILECITYONLINE.COM](mailto:INFO@MOBILECITYONLINE.COM) or by phone at 866-266-CITY.   
   
   If you would like to place an order, but do not wish to provide the necessary information to us online, you can provide us with the information over the phone by calling a customer service representative at 866-266-CITY.. They will gladly complete your order manually.   
   
   At any time you may correct/change any information that we may have on file. Please submit your changes via e-mail to [INFO@MOBILECITYONLINE.COM](mailto:INFO@MOBILECITYONLINE.COM) or call us at 866-266-CITY. You may also contact us in writing at:   
MOBILECITYONLINE  
CUSTOMER SERVICE  
299 BROADWAY SUITE 805  
NEW YORK NY 10007   
   
   If you elect to enter any contests or other promotions related to MOBILECITYONLINE.COM please note that, by entering, you are giving your permission to use your personal information for promotional purposes.   
   
**Accuracy and Typographical Errors**  
   MOBILECITYONLINE.COM aspires to publish accurate selling prices for the products we offer. However, on occasion we do make mistakes. In the event a product is listed at an incorrect price or with incorrect information due to a typographical error or error in pricing or product information received from our suppliers, MOBILECITYONLINE.COM shall have the right to refuse or cancel any such orders whether or not the order has been confirmed and your credit card has been charged. If your credit card has been charged for the purchase and your order is canceled, ElephantWireless.com shall immediately issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the charge.   
   
**Order Acceptance Policy**  
   Your receipt of an electronic or other form of order confirmation does not signify our acceptance of your order, nor does it constitute confirmation of our offer to sell. ElephantWireless.com reserves the right at any time after receipt of your order to accept or decline your order, without prior notice to you, to supply less than the quantity you ordered of any item. All orders must obtain pre-approval with an acceptable method of payment, as established by our credit and fraud avoidance department. We may require additional verifications or information before accepting any order. MOBILECITYONLINE.COM does not accept orders from customers who intend to resell the products offered by MOBILECITYONLINE.COM.   
   
**Sales Tax**  
   MOBILECITYONLINE.COM shall automatically charge and withhold the applicable sales tax for orders to be delivered to addresses within New York. Each customer shall be solely responsible for all sales taxes, or other taxes, on orders shipped to any other state.
